项目第28条
Item 28:
你为我取的爱称
your pet name for me.
时间不多了  你得下决定
Time's running out on this. You need to make a decision.
我发给你公证过的爱称提议表了
I submitted you a notarized list.
抱歉  你提的"咕噜"跟"疯婆子"不行好吗
I'm sorry, but "Gollum" and "Flakey" are not acceptable.
你也不喜欢"玉米公主"
Well, you don't like "Princess Corncob"
也不喜欢"费斯特"  你真是太难伺候了
you don't like "Fester"-- you're just impossible to please.
这项之后再说好了
We'll come back to that one.
现在到了我们的
This brings us to the final item
年度"感情发展高峰会"的最后项目
in our annual State of the Relationship Summit.
项目第29条  情人节
Item 29: Valentine's Day.
图穷匕就现了
Ah, the worst for last.
完全的疯婆作风
Classic Flakey.
先别不开心  我相信我已经想到了
Before you get upset, I believe I've come up with
一个既能庆祝节日  又能让你我
a way for us to celebrate the occasion
都开心的好计划
that we both can enjoy.
大多数人都是在会议开始前用笑话开场
People usually start a meeting with a joke,
但你继续  用笑话结尾也行
but you go ahead-- end with one.
我提议我们去纳帕谷酒庄的
I propose we spend a weekend
住宿加早餐酒店共度一个周末
at a bed-and-breakfast in Napa Valley.
我讨厌你句子里的每个字
I hate every word in that sentence.
包含"共度"  "去"  "我们"以及"一个"
Including "in" "at," "we" and "a".
为什么  谢尔顿  给个理由
Come on, Sheldon. Why not?
首先  住那种酒店就一定得跟
For starters, a bed-and-breakfast forces you
陌生人坐一起共进早餐
to eat with strangers at your table.
我早想到了
One step ahead of you--
伯纳黛特跟沃罗威茨会一起来
Bernadette and Wolowitz are going with us.
很好
Oh, very well.
那房间怎么安排
What are the sleeping arrangements?
我们才刚约会三年呢
We've only been dating for three years.
如果我们睡同一间  会被人说闲话的
If we were to share a room, people might talk.
我帮你订了自己一间
I got you your own room.
-万一我房里的是爪脚浴缸怎么办  -不是的
- What if my room has a claw-foot bathtub? - It doesn't.
我知道你会觉得那像是在怪兽肚里洗澡
I know it makes you feel like you're bathing inside a monster.
我很谢谢你的心意
Look, I appreciate the effort,
但我还是不知道
but I'm still unclear how this trip
这旅行有什么值得让我开心的地方
is supposed to be enjoyable for me.
我们的情人节晚餐的地点就在
We're going to have Valentine's Day dinner
一辆运作正常的古董火车上
on a fully functioning vintage train.
怎么古董  解释详细点
Vintage? Be specific.
美国铝业FA-4型柴油火车头
An Alcoa FA-4 diesel locomotive
拉着完美修复的
leading a train of meticulously restored
1915年款的普尔曼头等火车厢
1915 Pullman first-class coaches.
我有一股想抱你的冲动
I'm feeling the urge to hug you.
一  二...
And one... and two...
好了  咕噜  不用了
All right, Gollum, we're good.
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
生活大爆炸
第七季  第十五集
你们确定不跟我们一起去纳帕谷酒庄吗
Are you sure you guys don't want to come with us to Napa?
现在还来得及订房哦
You could probably still get a room.
不用了  我们就在家静度周末吧
No, I think we're just gonna have a quiet weekend at home.
而且我觉得带佩妮
Plus, I'm not sure it's a great idea
去生产酒的地方  不是个好主意
to take Penny to where wine comes from.
干嘛  开玩笑而已
What? It's a joke.
别这样  我们整天吐槽对方
Oh, come on. We bust on each other.
我戴傻逼眼镜  你可能有酗酒问题
I wear dorky glasses, you might have a problem--
就是图个乐嘛
it's all for laughs.
幸好我喝了有点晕乎  不然你死定了
That would really piss me off if I didn't have a buzz going on.
霍华德  你在火车上时会佩戴
Howard, which pocket watch will you be wearing
哪块怀表呢
for dinner on the train?
麻烦再说一次
I'm sorry, what?
我是怕如果我们戴了同一块表
Oh, I'm afraid if we wear the same pocket watch,
会很尴尬
it will be embarrassing.
-我没有任何怀表  -天啊
- I don't own a pocket watch. - Oh, my.
抱歉  我不应该提起你的痛处
Well, then my apologies for bringing up this sore spot.
既然你们两个情人节会在家
Since you two are gonna be around for Valentine's,
能帮忙我看一下小桂子吗
would you mind watching Cinnamon?
你丫情人节有约啊
You have Valentine's plans?!
语气有点夸张了  其实我没那么惊讶
Which came out sounding way more surprised than I meant.
我再重说一遍  你丫有...
L-Let me try that again. You have Val...
臣妾做不到啊
See? I can't do it.
我没有约  所以才订了那晚
I don't have plans, which is why I booked time
去看天文望远镜
on the big telescope that night.
整个夜晚都在看着满天星斗
Well, an evening looking at the stars--
感觉也挺浪漫的啊
that's still kind of romantic.
可我是独自一人看
Except I'll be alone.
救这场跟给猪画口红一样难  你配合点好吗
I'm trying to put lipstick on a pig here. Work with me.
-我们很乐意替你照看小桂子  -对
- We'd be happy to watch Cinnamon. - Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
我希望我跟它至少有一人能"看到好戏"
Oh, and I'd like for at least one of us to see some action,
所以如果你们两个要做爱
so if you guys happen to have sex,
碰巧她也在  就不要赶她了
it's cool if she stays in the room.
你们俩要"做"时  也别赶艾米哦
Hey, same goes for the two of you with Amy.
谢尔顿  你觉得如何
What do you think, Sheldon?
太厉害了
It's magnificent.
这将会是我最棒的一个情人节
This is going to be the best Valentine's Day ever.
我很高兴你喜欢
I'm so glad you like it.
我都准备要说出"我爱死了"
I'm prepared to say I love it,
但我要先检查  车上有没有流浪汉
as soon as I confirm there are no hobos aboard.
好
Okay.
拉杰  我知道了  再见
Raj, I got it. Bye.
刚才是你爸比
That was your daddy.
他要我跟你说他很想...
He wanted me to say that he misses...
我干嘛跟着他发狗痴啊
Why am I doing this?
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day!
有花又有巧克力
Ooh, flowers and chocolates?
有人今晚想扒我的小裤裤哟
Somebody's trying to get me out of my panties.
如果打开看到里面  少了五颗巧克力
Don't be surprised if you find five chocolates missing
以及三颗被人咬过椰子口味时  别吓到哦
and three gross coconut ones with a bite taken out.
我买来的时候就那样了
It came that way when I bought it.
我也给你买了点小礼物
Got you a little something, too.
珠宝首饰吗
Jewelry.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
湖人队的球票
Lakers tickets?!
更棒的是  不一定要带我去
It gets better. Instead of me,
你可以带其他爱看球的朋友去
you can take someone who will actually enjoy it.
-你是全天下最棒的男朋友了  -谢谢
- You are the best boyfriend ever. - Thank you.
说真的  求你别拉我去
Seriously, please don't make me go.
我们是不是该挪去房里再"庆祝"呢
Should we take this little party to the bedroom?
不用了  整个家只剩我们
Don't have to-- we have the whole place to ourselves.
-有道理  -而且只要你想要
- Oh, that's true. - In fact, if you want,
我们可以在谢尔顿的宝座上"做"
we can do it right here on Sheldon's spot.
这是我这辈子听到过最让人失"性"致的话
That is the least sexy thing anyone's ever said to me.
回房间吧
To the bedroom!
今晚的主菜特餐  是海鲜意大利调味饭
And for the entree, tonight's special is a seafood risotto.
有任何问题吗
Do you have any questions?
我有个问题
Uh, I do.
这火车车厢是用着原来的杆销联结器呢
Uh, does this train car have the original link-and-pin coupler
还是米勒式的
or the Miller Hook and Platform?
抱歉  我是指对食物方面的问题
I'm sorry, I meant questions about the food.
当然  那...
Oh, of course. Um...
这海鲜意大利调味饭是在
is the seafood risotto being served on a train car
用原装杆销联结器的车厢上提供呢
with the original link-and-pin coupler
还是在使用米勒式连接器的车厢上提供
or the Miller Hook and Platform?
我们还是待会儿再点菜吧
I-I think we're gonna need a minute.
有趣小知识  两者皆非
Fun fact: it's neither.
他们用的是AAR  E型的连接器
They actually use the AAR type E coupler.
如果你在火车头分开连接时仔细听
If you listen carefully when the locomotive disconnects,
你就能听到连接处
you'll hear the characteristic
招牌的哒  咻  砰声响
click-pshht-thunk of the knuckle.
我勒个去
Get out of town.
有趣小知识  我要跳火车自尽啦
Fun fact: I'm gonna jump off this train.
小桂子
Hey, Cinnamon,
猜猜谁刚才用人类式爽了一炮[对应狗爬式]
guess who just did it human style.
我的老天啊
Oh, my God!
喊的有点晚  不过我也接受了
It's a little late, but I'll take it.
不是啦  小桂子把巧克力都吃了
No, Cinnamon ate the chocolates.
巧克力会让狗狗致命的
That's really bad for dogs.
巧克力中含有可可碱  会作用于小狗的中枢神经和心肌
从而让狗狗中毒
糟糕  那我们该怎么办
Oh, crap. What are we gonna do?
我们应该立刻带她去看兽医
We gotta get her to a vet right now.
我不认识兽医
I don't have a vet.
我认识治足科的  验光配眼镜的  治过敏的
I have a podiatrist, an optometrist, an allergist,
还有治皮肤病和泌尿科的医生
a dermatologist, a urologist.
怪不得你会觉得我认识兽医
You'd think I'd have a vet.
离这不远有个兽医  咱们赶紧带她去
Okay. There's one not far from here. Come on. Let's go.
好的  库萨帕里说得对
Okay. Koothrappali was right.
我们演"动作片"时应该让她看着
We should have let her watch.
再来一个  再来一个
Do another one, do another one!
好的
Okay.
这是我对美铁阿西乐特快
Here's my impression of the Amtrak Acela
飞驰在东部走廊线上的印象
barreling down the Eastern Corridor.
你的嘴真能"跑火车"啊
It's like there's a train in your mouth.
对了  我也会一个
Oh, yeah. I've got one.
美铁狼獾号开进芝加哥时的火车声
Um, the Amtrak Wolverine coming into Chicago.
我坐过那趟火车
I've been on that train.
刚仿佛让我置身其中
And I just was again.
看看你们能不能猜到我是什么意思
Hey, see if you guys can guess this one.
中枪  脑肝涂地  倒地而亡
Bang! Splat! Thud.
-你坐过多少趟火车  -多了去了
- How many trains have you been on? - Tons.
六年前  我做快递时被一个箱子砸到脑袋
A box fell on my head at UPS six years ago.
现在就领领救济金  坐坐火车来打发时间
Now I just collect disability and ride trains.
你的生活真是太棒了
Your life's amazing.
不一直都是
Not always.
六年前  我做快递时被一个箱子砸到脑袋
A box fell on my head at UPS six years ago.
现在就领领救济金  坐坐火车来打发时间
Now I just collect disability and ride trains.
我干嘛要做这种无谓的尝试
Why do I even try?
-我去摆平它  -好吧
- I'm gonna fix this right now. - Okay.
尽量让现场看起来像一桩事故
Just make it look like an accident.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你在跟你的女朋友共进情人节晚餐呢
You are at Valentine's dinner with your girlfriend.
现在给我滚回去  坐回她旁边陪她
Now get back over there and be with her.
你说得对
You're right.
我真是太迟钝了
That was insensitive of me.
我得回我那桌了
I have to go back to my table now.
-你也一起来吧  -好的
- You should join us. - All right.
这下好了
Great.
要同时忍受俩极品
Now there's two of 'em.
她吃了多少巧克力
How much chocolate did she eat?
-一整盒  -说句公道话
- A whole box. - Well, to be fair,
你给我的时候  已经偷吃掉不少了
you ate a lot of it before you gave it to me.
所以在某种程度上  我可能救了她的狗命
So the point is I may have saved her life.
抱歉  你们觉得这很好笑吗
I'm sorry, is this a joke to you?
不是
No.
或许她觉得是
Maybe to her.
那盒巧克力有多大盒
How big a box of chocolate was it?
大约这么大  我不太记得了
Uh, something like this. I don't know.
那是我加满一箱油送的
It came free with a full tank of gas.
你不是吧
Really?
你知道那两张湖人的球票有多贵吗
Do you know how much those Lakers tickets were?
你知道现在汽油有多贵吗
Do you know how much gas is?
-抱歉  -抱歉
- Sorry. - Sorry.
老天爷  小桂子  你还好吗
Oh, my God, Cinnamon, are you okay?!
你们俩真是太过分了
I can't believe you two!
请你尽一切努力拯救她的生命
You do whatever it takes to save her life.
如果她需要新器官  我会去买任何能用的狗
If she needs new organs, I'll buy any dog necessary
然后撕了它们  把器官取出来
and scrap them for parts!
你是狗狗的主人吗
You're the owner?
主人  父亲兼灵魂伴侣
Owner, father, soul mate,
如果她有个三长两短  我还将是你们的恶梦
and if anything happens to her, your worst nightmare!
她现在没有出现呕吐
Well, she's not throwing up,
这是个好现象
which is a good sign.
我现在把她带进去  输点液
So, I'm gonna take her in back, put her on fluids
给她吃点能吸收毒素的药
and give her something to absorb the toxins.
-别担心  -好的  谢谢你
- Okay? - Okay, thank you.
如果她害怕  你可以唱歌给她听
Oh, if she's scared, you can sing to her.
她喜欢水果姐姐
She likes Katy Perry.
但千万别唱《烟火》
Oh, but don't do "Firework"
听到这首歌她会兴奋过头的
That gets her all riled up.
知道了
Got it.
当初真应该去学牙科
Should have been a dentist.
什么是美国建造过最棒的
Okay, what was the best four-ten-four
4-10-4设计类型的火车头是哪款
U.S. Locomotive ever built?
这是陷阱题  因为从来就没有建过
Trick question. There never was one.
抑或曾经有过
Or was there?
神马
What?!
1944年  太平洋铁路公司建造出第6131号火车头
In 1944, the Pacific Railroad built number 6131,
重新配置了传动器和气缸
which rearranged the drivers and cylinders,
解决了Q-1的问题
solving the problem of the Q-1,
并创造了双驱动的4-4-6-4型
creating a duplex-drive four-four-six-four.
在哪个美好世界
In what world is
4-4-6-4会是4-10-4啊
a four-four-six-four a four-ten-four?
一个我不想存在的世界
A world I don't want to live in!
说真的  我有种股想"与世长辞"的冲动
Seriously, I no longer want to live in this world.
戴上你车长思考帽
Hold on to your conductor's hat.
如果你曲柄转动第二个和第三个车轴
You crank the second and third axles,
创造出一对内部连杆
creating a pair of internal connecting rods,
4-10-4型就诞生啦
and boom-- four-ten-four.
如果你仔细想想  Q2型
If you think about it, the Q-2
就像是美国从未创造出的4-10-4型号
was like the four-ten-four America never made.
这下我会忍不住一直想的
I may never stop thinking about it.
艾米  我们能遇见这家伙的几率是多少啊
Amy, what are the odds we run into this guy?
比你想象中多得多
Better than you think.
如果你客气地问乘务员
You know, if you ask nicely,
他们会让你去参观引擎舱
they'll let you visit the engine room.
我希望这一天永不结束
I never want this day to end.
已经感觉像永远不会结束了
It's feeling like it never will.
走吧
Come on.
我有告诉你  我当快递时发生过什么意外吗
Hey, did I tell you what happened to me at UPS?
好像情人节对我的打击还不够大
As if Valentine's Day wasn't bad enough,
你们还想害死我的狗
you try to kill my dog?!
居然还是用便宜的巧克力
And with cheap chocolate, no less?
那不是便宜货
It wasn't cheap.
那是免费白送的
It was free.
我们真的很抱歉  那是个意外
We're really sorry. It was an accident.
对啊  我们不在客厅也没多久
Yeah, we weren't even out of the room that long.
拜托  好一阵子好吗
Oh, no, come on. It was a while.
好一阵子呢
It was a while.
小桂子没事吧
Oh, is Cinnamon gonna be okay?
她反应良好
She's responding well.
我们只需要要她留院多观察一会
We just want to keep her a little longer for observation.
好的  可以让我进去看看她吗
All right. Uh, would-would it be okay for me to see her?
平常这时候我们都上床睡觉了
We're usually in bed by now,
我想让她知道  我就在她身边
and I want her to know that I'm here.
是啦  我们同睡一张床  有时还跟对方抱抱
Yes, we sleep together, and sometimes we spoon.
没关系  我也跟我的狗狗一起睡
It's okay. I sleep with my dog, too.
虽然有规定不让外人进去
We're not supposed to let people in back,
但我可以破例一次
but I think I can make an exception.
-谢谢你  -进去吧
- Thank you. - Come on.
对了  我唱水果姐姐的歌给她听了
By the way, I sang her Katy Perry.
-是吗  -我才不管
- Oh, yeah? - And I don't care
里面那只令人讨厌的鹦鹉在嚷什么
what that obnoxious parrot back there says.
姐唱得可棒了
I crushed it.
我觉得他们俩之间会擦出爱的火花哟
I think there's something going on between the two of them.
或许吧  但你也觉得九分钟不算久
Maybe, but you also think nine minutes isn't a while,
所以你懂个屁啊
so what do you know?
-你没事吧  -干嘛这么问
- You okay? - Why?
因为我男友跟某个怪胎一起去玩火车了吗
Because my boyfriend's off playing choo-choo with some weirdo?
凭良心说  他俩都是怪胎
Well, to be fair, they're both weirdos.
我居然会以为今晚他会有所不同
I don't know what made me think tonight would be any different.
你能让他来这里  就已经很了不起了
Well, just the fact that you got him up here still says a lot.
说实话  我跟华仔赌两百块
To be honest, I bet Howie 200 bucks
说谢尔顿不可能会来
it wasn't gonna happen.
这下我能去乐高积木店买个超酷的R2机器人了
I'm going to the Lego store to get a big-ass R2-D2.
瞧  不仅是谢尔顿
See? It's not just Sheldon.
男人全是白痴
They're all idiots.
她说得对
She's right.
你男友是个待整改户又如何
So, your boyfriend's a fixer-upper.
大多数男人都是
Most of them are.
看这个家伙
I mean, look at this guy.
你觉得他生来就这么乖巧吗
You think he came like this?
我认识他时  他只是个性感的笨阿呆
When I met him, he was a hot, goofy mess.
现在他连太空都去过了
Now, he's been to space.
全是姐教育有方
That's all me.
也有点我自己的因素吧
I had a little to do with it.
当然啦
Oh, sure you did.
谁是妈咪的太空小英雄
Who's Mama's big space man?
人家啦
I am.
他们都进去半个小时了
They've been in there, like, half an hour.
为以后定个标准  这时间才能算"好一阵"
Yeah, for future reference, that's a while.
-我们要待多久  -不知道
- How long should we stay? - I don't know.
我有点饿了
I'm kind of hungry.
我看到隔壁有泰式餐厅
I saw a Thai place next door.
好的
Oh. Okay.
-回来啦  -她怎么样啦
- Hey! - How's she doing?
-她还好吗  -她没事了
- How is everything? - Yeah. She's gonna be okay;
-医生说可以带她回家了  -太好了
- they're gonna let me take her home. - Oh, good.
我需要你在接下来24小时
So I want you to keep a close eye on her
密切留意她
for the next 24 hours.
这里是一些要留意的警告信号
Here are a few warning signs to look out for,
你看到了  就马上打电话给我
and if you see any of them, don't hesitate to call.
非常感谢你这么照顾我家闺女
Thank you for taking such good care of my little girl.
我的荣幸  晚安
My pleasure. Have a nice night.
-感谢你的帮助  -是的
- Yes, thank you for all your help. - Yeah.
抱歉让你觉得我们不重视
I'm sorry if you didn't think we were taking it seriously.
其实我们热爱动物
We love animals.
你们俩有养宠物吗
Oh, do you guys own any pets?
-没有  -太好了
- No. - Good.
我好爱你
I love you so much.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
-抱歉  -不好意思
- Sorry. - Sorry.
你们错过了不少乐子
You guys missed a pretty great time.
列车长的怀表和我的一样
The conductor and I have the same pocket watch.
太疯狂了
It was crazy.
我能说疯子吗[火车头]
Dare I say "loco"?
艾米  你猜怎样
Oh, and, Amy, guess what?
列车长说他一下班
The conductor said as soon as he gets off work,
就可以去咱们住的那家酒店
he can come back to the bed and breakfast
为咱们演奏班卓琴
and play his banjo for us.
好了  我要和我的男友私下谈谈
Okay. I need to speak to my boyfriend in private,
现在就要谈
like, right now.
有节车厢是玻璃车顶
There's a car with a glass roof.
想去看星星吗
Want to go look at the stars?
听起来好浪漫哦
Oh, that sounds so romantic.
你们俩有完没完
Oh, give it a rest!
我们走
Let's go.
你怎么还在这里
Why are you still here?
不好意思
Excuse me.
你这样有点不礼貌哦
I think you're being a little rude.
我不礼貌
I'm being rude?
是你一整晚对我不礼貌吧
You've been rude to me this entire evening.
怎么可能
How is that possible?
我上火车后  几乎没和你说过话
I've hardly spoken to you since we got on the train.
我感觉到你们之间有一些摩擦
I'm detecting a little friction between you two,
我不想做第三轨
and I don't want to be a third rail.
懂我笑点吗
Get it?
当然
I get it.
走开啦
Leave!
你是怎么回事
What is your problem?
今天是情人节
It's Valentine's Day.
我们应该共度一个浪漫的周末
We're supposed to be having a romantic weekend.
是吗  因为我记得你说过
Oh, really? Because I remember you saying
这次的旅行是我们两个都能开心的
that this trip was going to be something we could both enjoy.
你是真心的
Did you mean that,
还是只是想骗我来
or were you just trying to trick me?
好吧  是我骗了你
Fine, it's true.
浪漫之夜是我应得的
I deserve romance,
但我不知道还有什么办法能令浪漫成真
and I didn't know how else to make it happen.
如果你要浪漫  那咱们就来浪漫吧
Well, if you want romance, then let's have romance!
看  红酒
Oh, look, there's wine.
好烧的葡萄汁
Grape juice that burns.
现在咱们凝视彼此的眼睛吧
Uh, now let's gaze into each other's eyes, hmm?
你眨眼了  我赢了
You blinked. I win.
-谢尔顿  -我想想  接下来做什么
- Sheldon... - Let's see. What's next?
对了  亲吻很浪漫
Oh, kissing's romantic.
刚才真不错
That was nice.
很好
Good.
列车长说如果我再去引擎室
The conductor said if I come back to the engine room,
他会教我怎么把火车开过交叉口
he'd show me how to bring the train through a crossing.
好的  玩得开心点
Okay, have fun.
你想和我一起去吗
Do you want to come with me?
可以吗  我想去
Really? I do.
两位  等等我
Hey, guys, wait up!
好啦
There you go.
好舒服好暖和哦
All cozy wozy.
看看医生说要注意观察什么
Here, let's see what the doctor says to keep an eye out for.
"拉杰什  我本来很害怕独自过情人节
"Rajesh, I was dreading Valentine's Day.
多谢你与我共度  伊薇特"
Thank you for spending it with me. Yvette."
小桂子  她把电话号码给我了
Cinnamon, she-she gave me her phone number.
早知道这么容易
If I knew it was that easy,
几个月前我就应该考虑给你下毒
I would have considered poisoning you months ago.
我应该说什么呢
Oh, what should I say?
我知道了  我就说她的名字是伊薇特
Oh, I know. I'll point out her name's Yvette,
所以她是兽医[同音]
and that she's a vet.
太好笑了
That's hysterical.
她会喜欢的
She'll love it.
-你好  -你回来啦
- Hello. - You're back.
-旅行如何  -太棒了
- How was your trip? It was wonderful!
太好了  发生了什么事
Great. What did you do?
我交了位新朋友
I made a new friend
他和我一样喜欢火车
who likes trains as much as I do,
我和艾米接吻了
uh, I kissed Amy on the lips,
还有  列车长为我演奏了班卓琴
and, uh, the conductor played his banjo for me.
晚安
Good night.
慢着  慢着
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
我想听一些细节
I'm gonna need more details.
我的新朋友叫埃里克
Oh, well, my new friend's name was Eric.
艾米嘴唇  有晚餐吃的巧克力蛋糕味
Um, Amy lips tasted like the brownie we had for dessert.
演奏班卓琴的列车长
the banjo-playing conductor
少了一根指头
was missing a finger,
但他用乐观精神弥补了
but he made up for it with his can-do attitude.
不  慢着慢着
No, hang on. Hang on.
这三件事对你来说都能相提并论吗
Are all those things equal to you?
我还真没考虑过  哪件才是最爱的事
It never occurred to me to pick a favorite.
好好考虑下
Well, give it a go.
不收集附加数据  我无法回答这个问题
I can't answer that without collecting additional data.
还"附加数据"呢  你个色狼[狗]
Additional data. You dog!
我不太确定聆听其他九指班卓琴演奏者表演
I'm not sure how listening to other nine-fingered banjo players
会让我成为狗  不过没关系
makes me dog, but all right.